Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/corneliuswinter--930a35 (LinkedIn) www.365sherpas.com (Company)

Top Skills

Reputation Management Issues Management Public Relations

Cornelius Winter

365 Sherpas. Part of Hirschen Group.

Berlin Metropolitan Area

Summary

Experienced Senior Partner and Entrepreneur with a demonstrated history of working in the management consulting industry. Strong research professional skilled in Corporate and Public Affairs, Political Communication, Policy Analysis and Advice, Governmental Affairs, and Corporate Social Responsibility.

Experience

365 Sherpas - Corporate Affairs & Policy Advice Founder, Principal Partner October 2013 - Present (8 years 7 months)
Berlin Area, Germany

Founder, Equity Partner

HERING SCHUPPENER Consulting - Corporate Affairs & Public Strategies GmbH

Managing Director

April 2012 - September 2013 (1 year 6 months)

Ketchum Pleon Holding GmbH Equity Partner January 2007 - March 2012 (5 years 3 months)

Ketchum Pleon GmbH / Ketchum Pleon Europe Managing Partner; Director Europe, Public Affairs July 2001 - March 2012 (10 years 9 months)

Plato Kommunikation GmbH / Scholz & Friends Group Director Government
January 2000 - July 2001 (1 year 7 months)

Deutscher Bundestag (German Parliament) Political Assistant 1998 - 1999 (1 year) DeutschlandRadio Berlin Free Lancer 1997 - 1999 (2 years)

European Parliament Political Assistant 1996 - 1998 (2 years)

Education

Humboldt University of Berlin Law

Freie Universität Berlin Political Sciences